JOSÉ PAIVA

DEVELOPER

Download PDF

josm142@gmail.com

Profile

A developer with a journalist soul, with a strong interest in new technologies. My experience in the world of journalism and business communications allows me to work as a bridge between technical and non-tecnical areas, in order to achieve the best result in every project.

Skills

Experience Developer

More than 5 years working as a wordpress/frontend developer and tech. consultant

Focus

on communication

Always searching ways to improve the interaction between tech and non tech areas. Constantly looking for feedback to improve

Desire to master JS

Focusing right now in learning everything I can to get more deep in Javascript World.

Technical

HTML	React	Typescript
CSS3	React Native	Node.js
Sass	Ionic	РНР
Javascript	Three.js	Wordpress
jQuery	Motion UI with JS	Codeigniter

Experience

Altimea S.A.C

Fullstack developer

Fullstack developer working mainly as technical-leader in React.js/Javascript projects

2018-currently

2017-Currently

Amas Digital

Main tech. consultant

Working as a freelancer consultant and helping develop wordpress sites and plugins. I also help business to use technology to improve their revenue

Full time Freelance developer

2017-2018

Worked as a full time wordpress developer. I was responsible for the whole infraestructure and project development for each client

Content Creator / Developer Grupo Panamericana de Radios

2012-2016

Started as a content creator/local reporter and helped create the first digital content and marketing area in the company. At first, I was responsible of creating interesting content for the company website and also make changes in the code, but after a while my role change to a more tech-focused one and I was responsible of implementing new software in the company to help their digital strategy

Journalism experience

2012-2013

Started as a reporter for local news in RBC Tv and then move to write notes for the digital edition of a News Magazine (Panamericana Television), after that I move to travel journalism working for Travel Update

Education

University San Martin de Porres

Major, Communication Science

I.C.P.N.A

Finished English Teaching/Speaking Advance Module

José Paiva — <u>josm142@gmail.com</u>